Screw yağmurl
Danny
Tracy
Big
Danny
Cincinnati
nước
So
Danny
Savannah
I'm
ML
estar
Wow
I'll see you next time.
The Judicial Island. Full view of Eni's Lobby.
Huh? Luno disappeared?
Nothing of the sort. That's the power of his Door Door fruit.
He can create a door out of thin air, then use it to travel to another location.
At any rate, don't bother trying to escape. It's simply not possible.
Let Robin go!
A finger pistol.
Usa!
Tired body.
Your last kick was a lot stronger. Tired already.
Stubborn one, aren't you?
Stop it!
I promise. I have no intention of running away.
I'll honor the deal. You don't have to hurt them.
They're the ones who keep attacking me. What do you expect?
Then let's hurry and leave before they get up again.
Wait!
It's all right, Robin. We'll be fine.
I understand what's going on. You're still hiding something from us, aren't you?
There's one last thing. You can do what you want.
But a pirate isn't allowed to leave their crew unless they have their captain's permission.
So no matter what, you can always believe in Luffy.
How!
How?
Robin, don't go!
You can say what you like to her, but she won't break our agreement.
How do you know that?
Long ago.
An island was erased.
Yes.
That is to say, the Navy issued a buster call and burned it to the ground without leaving
a single trace behind.
The only survivor of that incident was Nico Robin, still a child at the time.
She never told us.
Five vice-admirals and ten battleships are a terrifying force for anyone to behold.
For a child to see them destroy her home.
Well, it's nothing short of a nightmare.
Those thoughts have haunted her for years.
And now that her old nightmare bears its fangs at her companions, she no longer has the
will to resist us.
Bastards.
You knew.
And you used that.
Of course we did.
This is sick.
You people are sick!
You hear me?!
All of this is for the sake of justice.
I sympathize with her, but I cannot be swayed.
Don't give me that crap!
This isn't over!
Hey!
Hurry up and take a seat, Nico Robin.
We'll be at Eni's lobby shortly.
Wait!
What the hell's going on?!
Get back here!
You hear me?!
Are you sure about this?
Shouldn't we split those two up?
At this point, there's nothing they can do.
We've almost reached our destination anyway.
Their hope must be exhausted by now.
All they can do is quietly await their execution.
Let them lament their fates in silence until then.
The mating call is aיר that will work.
Not to hide, if you can harm you to come out.
I'm wondering, why do you push me rolling in this town?
What?
Patrick.
I be tracking your son out.
You betterolf.
I'm thinking, well, you're not...!
What's wrong, Roig!?
Dumpfrog!
Let off!
Don't garrow me, you big slimy jerk!
You realize that slap of yours derailed our train, don't you?
Froggy, turn back! Get out of the way!
We were about to catch up with Sanji too!
Now apologize!
Dumpfrog!
I'm gonna beat you!
I don't know what's going on out there right now, but it can't be good.
Hey, are you guys all right?
I guess so.
Help, my back!
Oh no! Our Kingfos are gone!
They disappeared!
No way! But how?
No, we're the ones who disappeared.
Our train probably got derailed back there.
Ah! Wow, that's even worse!
What now?
Well, there's not much we can do since we're completely off course.
We're gonna die! We're lost in sea forever!
No way!
At a time like this?
This guy's winning a million!
There we go.
That frog has some bad timing, but I can't stay mad at him.
Everyone still alive?
Yeah, somehow.
Stupid Yokozuna!
Well, at least they're spunky.
Hey!
Yeah?
Are we gonna be okay or what?
If we can't make it to Annie's lobby, I'm gonna be really pissed off!
Shut your trap and give me a second trying to warp!
Oh, that's weird.
Think there's something funny going on with this current.
Seems like we're stuck.
Kokoro?
Huh?
Do you know which direction to go?
Yeah, of course I do!
When we built the sea trains, we equipped them with eternal poses set to all the islands
with stations on them.
Then we'll be fine.
I'll watch the sea.
You just steer.
Huh?
You sure that'll help?
I'm a navigator.
I got this.
I see.
Huh?
That's good to know!
Oh, almost forgot.
Hey, Yokozuna!
Stop wrestling and get your froggy butt off of here!
Get off!
He ran away!
Get her!
What was that?
You're glad I'm still okay?
How sweet.
I know you were just trying to save me, but you jumped the gun.
These folks didn't kidnap me.
Does this mean Granny can speak frog?
Yeah.
What are you guys looking at?
That ugly old lady is talking to a giant frog!
Oh, I get it!
Granny was a frog all along!
Mom!
She never quite passed as a human now, did she?
You realize you guys are gonna get hit for that later, don't you?
No kidding.
Hello!
Straw Hat!
Rocket Man!
And you see them yet?
No.
I got nothing.
Damn!
That stupid frog.
That thing must have sent them flying a million miles away!
Hey!
Don't start losing hope on me!
We set out to save our bro Frankie and we won't stop till we make it happen!
That's right!
All we can do now is keep on heading to Annie's Lobby and have faith that Rocket Man is gonna
meet us whenever we get there!
Go!
Sodom!
Gomorrah!
Huh?
Hey!
Hold on!
What's that over there?
It looks like there's another train car floating just ahead of us!
It could be full of enemies!
Alright guys, let's prepare for battle!
Yeah!
Ahoy!
Is anyone in there?
We're the Frankie family!
Come out and show yourself!
Hey!
I see someone!
It's that dude with the swirly eyebrows!
Annie's Lobby Department of Management here.
Is everything in order regarding the transfer?
Yes.
We will be delivering the two criminals on schedule.
We can see the island now, so expect us soon.
Understood.
We'll make preparations for your return.
I can't help but feel a business-
we don't feel a business at all.
Wal Recognies
When I fall, one thing I can touch you
was in my space.
Just finish it and set it away.
When it begins to bail,
the future never falls apart.
It can never follow me so fast.
You can never go,
笑顔と涙を積み重ねてゆく。
どんなに闇の深い夜でも 必ず明日は来るから。
I'm gonna bring down the whole island!
We have Sanji and Usa... I mean, Sniper King to help us, too!
They're gonna have to wait in line,
cause I got a lot of bashing to do!
On the next, One Piece!
Landing operation start!
Charge in, Straw Hats!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!